Guide to the Records and Papers of Terry Sanford, 1945-1998 UA.03.60.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series 6. Covington/Ellis Book Materials
  - Terry Sanford Collection UNC-CH/SFC/FT93003 T-3531
    - T-.058 copy, 1961 20 December (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0099)
    - T-.059 copy, 1962 11 January (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0100)
    - T-.060 copy, 1962 18 January (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0101)
    - T-.071 copy WSIC Radio Statesville, NC Public Service Announcement, 1962 6 June (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0102)
    - T-.072 one side only, c.96, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0103)
    - T-.073 c.96, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0104)
    - T-.074 copy (mislabeled T3731.074), undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0105)
    - T-.075 copy, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0106)
    - T-.076-077 copy Side A: T-.076 8/8/62 Side B: T-.077 8/15/62, 1962 8-15 August (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0107)
    - T-.078-079 copy Side A: T-.078 8/23/62 Side B: T-.079 9/6/62, 1962 August 23 - 1962 September 6 (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0108)
    - T-.080 copy, 1962 11 September (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0109)
    - T-.081 copy, 1962 17 September (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0110)
    - T-.082 copy, 1962 3 October (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0111)
    - T-.083 copy, 1962 4 October (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0112)
    - T-.084 copy, 1962 11 October (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0113)
    - T-.087 copy, 1962 8 November (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0114)
    - T-.088 copy, 1962 15 November (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0115)
    - T-.089 copy, 1962 16 November (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0116)
    - T-.090 copy, 1962 21 November (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0117)
    - T-.092 copy, 1962 6 December (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0118)
    - T-.093 copy, 1962 10 December (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0119)
    - T-.094 copy, 1962 20 December (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0120)
    - T-.095 copy, [1962?] (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0121)
    - T-.096 copy "Midnight to Reveille", 1962 (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0122)
    - T-.100 copy, 1963 9 January (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0123)
    - T-.101 copy, 1963 18 January (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0124)
    - T-.102 copy, 1963 18 January (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0125)
    - T-.107 copy, 1963 15 March (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0126)
    - T-.108 copy, 1963 27 March (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0127)
    - T-.113 copy, 1963 21 May (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0128)
    - T-.114 copy, 1963 24 May (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0129)
    - T-.115 copy, 1963 17 June (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0130)
    - T-.116 copy, 1963 18 June (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0131)
    - T-.121 copy, 1963 12 July (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0132)
    - T-.122 copy, 1963 18 July (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0133)
    - T-.123 copy, 1963 24 July (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0134)
    - T-.124 copy, 1963 26 July (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0135)
    - T-.125 copy, 1963 9 September (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0136)
    - T-.127 copy, 1963 30 September (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0137)
    - T-.128 copy, 1963 9 October (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0138)
    - T-.129 copy, 1963 11 October (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0139)
    - T-.130 copy, 1963 14 October (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0140)
    - T-.131 copy, 1963 27 December (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0141)
    - T-.136 copy (10 February 1964 Part I), 1964 10 February (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0142)
    - T-.137 copy (10 February 1964 Part II), 1964 10 February (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0143)
    - T-.141 copy, 1964 18 April (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0144)
    - T-.142 copy, 1964 20 April (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0145)
    - T-.143 copy, 1964 30 April (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0146)
    - T-.145 copy, 1964 18 June (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0147)
    - T-.146 copy (N.B. Date may not be correct. The tape box indicates the above date, but a label on the reel indicates a Jan 5, 1965 date (Address to Good Neighbor Council, Winston-Salem) - contents do not seem to match, though.), 1964 25 June (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0148)
    - T-.147 copy, 1964 30 June (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0149)
    - T-.148 copy, 1964 23 July (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0150)
    - T-.149 copy, 1964 29 July (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0151)
    - T-.151 copy, 1964 15 August (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0152)
    - T-.152 copy, 1964 1 September (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0153)
    - T-.153 copy, 1964 4 September (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0154)
    - T-.154 copy, 1964 1 October (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0155)
    - T-.156 copy, 1964 4 November (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0156)
    - T-.159 copy, 1964 4 December (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0157)
    - T-.161 copy, 1965 6 January (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0158)
    - T-.162 copy from WBT Radio, Charlotte, NC, undated (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0159)
    - T-.164 copy, 1972 11 April (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0160)
    - T-.166 copy, 1972 2 May (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0161)
    - T-.174, .180, .186 copy Side B: Gov. Sanford on Art Lindetta Show, undated (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0162)
    - T-.192 copy, undated (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0163)
    - T-.193 copy (Tape 1 of 2), undated (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0164)
    - T-.193 copy (Tape 2 of 2), undated (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0165)
    - T-.194 copy, undated (Box 181, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0166)